

# ABDERRAOUF ABDI

FULL STACK JS MOBILE WEB DEVELOPER



El Hamma Gabes Tunisie



abdiabderraouf@gmail.com



216 97 276 139

#### **PROFIL**

Developer and experienced teacher with 16 years in computer education and works in freelance web development and 3 years in web and mobile development within a development startup in Tunisia.

able to work as a FrontEnd developer with Angular Framework or React library or as a backend developer with Nodejs.

#### INTERESTS

- ✓ Technology
- ✓ Travel
- ✓ Sport: Natation, football, Handball.
- ✓ Musique.
- ✓ Sciences.

### **LANGUAGES**

Arabe

French

English

German

# **SKILLS**

Html, Css, Bootstrap

React

Angular

Java Script

Nodejs express mongodb

Php wordpress

Python

Jira, Agil, Scrum



#### **EDUCATION**

1998 - 2003

Univercity of Sfax , Tunisia

Masters in IT Management

University of Sfax: Faculty of Economics Management of Sfax

2003 - 2005

Gabes, Tunisie

Diploma of complementary studies:

University of Gabes: higher institute of technological studies

## **EXPERIENCES**

Sep. 2006 -March 2023

ElHamma, Tunisie

#### Ministry of Education

High school computer teacher

Works as a freelancer in php java script web development

- \* Teaching algorithms and Pascal language in secondary school
- \*Teaching design and development of websites with html, css and java script.
- \* Teaching Sql databases and DBMS Access
- \* Teaching python: turtle, data analysis with pandas

May. 2022- May. 2023

Gabes, Tunisie

#### Protech-it: startup

Full Stack is Developer

Development of Angular frontend projects.

Development of frontend react projects.

Development of Nodejs backend projects.

Development of wordpress projects.